# STEVE ROLLINS FULL TIME STUDENT

- coding61.sr@gmail.com
- **\** 206-940-5274
- **♀** North Bend, WA
- in steven-rollins
- greenhornsr

While I have spent more than 10 representative; my new passion and ambitions reside as a web developer that excels at my craft. I have spent several months primarily learning about HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REACT, REDUX, HOOKS, NODEJS, KNEX, SQL, SQLITE3, POSTGRES & more. I also have SWIFT, & more. My goal is to find a place of employment where my passion for developing quality applications improves the quality of life & experiences for end users; increases value and I can continue to grow as a contributor with an equally strong, reciprocal team that people and developer work as I

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT

нти

CSS

JavaScript

NodeJS

React

Redux

SQL

GraphQL

Python

PostgreSQL

Less/S

Django

Angular

SALES

Mobility

Business Solutions

IoT

Retail

SMB

Enterpris

Healthcare Hardware

Software

#### **Education**

Lambda School Apr. 2019 to Current

Coding Dojo

## **Employment**

Lambda School

Team Lead(REMOTE)

North Bend, WA Aug. 2019 to Nov. 2019

Oct. 2016 to Jan. 2017

Full Time position. Primary responsibility was to support the learning and professional growth of Lambda Students. Often required mentoring students in the understanding of HTML, CSS, JS, REACT, HOOKS, REDUX, CONTEXT, EXPRESS, NODE.js, SQLITE3/PSQL and other associated concepts.

Verizon

Bellevue, WA

Major Accounts Manager - Healthcare

June 2013 to May 2015

Responsible for identifying and introducing HIPAA compliant partner solutions that solved mobility needs of western Washington's largest healthcare systems; keeping security, industry regulations, budgets and most importantly...patient safety front of mind.

Verizon Wireless

Denver, CO

**Business Account Executive** 

Nov. 2007 to June 2013

New business customer procurement, management of existing customer base for businesses that had employee counts mostly ranging from 5-499.

### **Projects**

Chicago Array of Things

June 2019 to June 2019

Chicago Array of Things was a project where, in 5 days, a cross function team of UI, WEB: FE, BE, Data Scientists were expected to build out a complete web application that connected to the chicago aot API and rendered information that best represented environment data sourced from specific sensors a user wanted to visualize. I was FE on this project.

YELP-FEELERS

Oct. 2019 to Oct. 2019

YELP FEELERS was a project where, in 5 days, a cross functional team of UI, WEB: FE, BE, Data Scientists were expected to build out a complete web application that connected to the YELP API and created the ability to MODIFY user star review scores based on substance of their written reviews to making it a more accurate depiction/review.

#### **Awards**

Verizon Wireless Mountain Region · Winner's Circle

2010

Award given to sales representatives performing in the top 5% of ALL peer Key Performance metrics (new customers, renewed customers, IoT, messaging, data, etc.)

#### **Activities**

Learning!

Lifting

Basketball

Soccer

### Volunteering

Mt. Si View (SVSD) · Head Coach Basketball

Developing, leading, teaching 8-11 year old boys basic and advanced basketball skills.

i-9 Sports  $\cdot$  Flag Football Assistant Coach

Teaching 6-7 year old boys Flag Football

I-9 Sports · Soccer Assistant Coach

Teaching 4-5 year olds how to play soccer.